[
   {
      "title":"问题 1",
      "question":"Events that cannot occur together in a single trial are known as :",
      "answer":"Mutually Exclusive"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 2",
      "question":"A project that is experiencing constant Communication Blockers is most likely to",
      "answer":"Have conflict occur"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 3",
      "question":"A project manager is going to use the milestone chart. In what situation is it most relevant totuse the milestone chart ?",
      "answer":"When reporting to senior management"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 4",
      "question":"You are due to start work on a new project and have recently been handed the approved ProjecttCharter. What is the first thing you must do ?",
      "answer":"Identify the stakeholders involved in giving their input on the scope of thetprojec"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 5",
      "question":"A project team is working on a project that includes people working in 5 different locationstincluding France, India, USA, Australia  and Dubai. There are over 123 main employees intthe team. Which of the following can have the Biggest Impact in making the dynamics of thetproject easier to manage :",
      "answer":"Staffing Management Plan"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 6",
      "question":"While working on your project, you identify a new risk at 50 percent project completion. There ista very high probability the risk will occur on the project, while at the same time, it istexpected to have a low impact. Which of the following mitigation strategies would you use ?",
      "answer":"You will add the risk to the watch list"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 7",
      "question":"When it comes to integration, the project manager is mainly responsible for :",
      "answer":"Making sure the aspects of the project are in smooth coordination with onetanother"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 8",
      "question":"Given the circumstances surrounding the project, The project manager has decided to Fast Tracktthe Project. This will likely result in:",
      "answer":"A Smaller duration of the project"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 9",
      "question":"Which of the following is the definitive list of constraints on a project :",
      "answer":"Scope, time, cost , quality, risk , resources, customer satisfaction"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 10",
      "question":"Which of the following would a project manager consider as an example of a Cost Plus Fixed FeetContract?",
      "answer":"Cost plus $30,000 as fee"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 11",
      "question":"A project manager has correctly decided to address a risk by using passive risk acceptance. Whattsort of a situation do you think he must have been faced with ?",
      "answer":"A situation in which the risk would be dealt with as it occurred"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 12",
      "question":"Currently, there are 7 people in the project team. 2 more resources are added later on in thetproject's life. What is the number of the additional channels of communication ?",
      "answer":"15"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 13",
      "question":"From amongst the contract types listed below, The _____________ contract has the most cost risktfor the buyer",
      "answer":"Cost Plus Percentage of Costs (CPPC)"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 14",
      "question":"While working as a project manager for a leading Technology consulting firm, you were involved inta project which had a budget of $93000 with a duration of 1.5 months. You have currently spentt$35000 to complete the work which was originally expected to cost $39000. As per your schedule,tyou should have spent $40,000 by this time. How would you describe your project ?",
      "answer":"Under Budget"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 15",
      "question":"The difference between contingency reserves and management reserves is that",
      "answer":"Contingency reserves are the known unknowns on a project while the managementtreserves are the unknown unknowns on a project"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 16",
      "question":"The communications management plan is developed on a project while keeping in view the needs oftthe",
      "answer":"Stakeholders"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 17",
      "question":"The following is an appropriate description of why quality is planned in as opposed to beingtinspected into the project",
      "answer":"Inspecting Quality is more expensive than Planning Quality"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 18",
      "question":"You recently joined a new organization where you have been given the responsibility of leadingtthe project management office. What is the FIRST thing you should do ?",
      "answer":"Talk to the main stakeholders to develop an understanding of the organizationtand its projects."
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 19",
      "question":"Which of the following can include information such as : Source of the requirements, Requirementtidentification number, person assigned for managing the requirement",
      "answer":"Requirements Traceability Matrix"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 20",
      "question":"One of your key suppliers for an important deliverable is constantly making delays in submittingthis work to your project. You decide to deal with the situation when you have more timetavailable from your current workload. You are using the conflict resolution technique known as :",
      "answer":"Withdrawing"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 21",
      "question":"Which of the following is so important  that they should always be included on the list oftitems under discussion at all team meetings.",
      "answer":"Discussing the risks on the project"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 22",
      "question":"You are working on a global partnership project in the Airline Industry. Till now , you have beentdiligently tracking the progress of your project via Earned Value Management (EVM).  ThetActual costs on the project are $ 700 milllion, while your cost variance is $200 million. Thetschedule Variance shows a value of -$100 million. What are the values of SPI, CPI and PV ?",
      "answer":"0.9,1.28,1000"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 23",
      "question":"While working on your construction project, you come across environmental risks that couldtnegatively effect the project. It would be best to hire a consultant to share insights andtadvice on tackling the challenges. Which contract type should be used for hiring the consultantt?",
      "answer":"Time and Material"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 24",
      "question":"While negotiating with external supplier stakeholders, how important do you think are nonverbaltcommunications for a project manager ?",
      "answer":"Very important"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 25",
      "question":"In project management terms, what is known as a heuristic?",
      "answer":"A rule that is generally accepted"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 26",
      "question":"A member of your team informs you that she does not know which project is the most important onetout of the several projects she is working on. In a large organization, who is responsible fortdetermining the priorities between the different projects  ?",
      "answer":"PMO ( Project Management Office)"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 27",
      "question":"At the recent meeting, you discover that the customer is not satisfied with a certain deliverabletof the project. What is the Best thing to do?",
      "answer":"Ask the customer why they are not satisfied with the deliverable"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 28",
      "question":"In the Salience Model, Stakeholders are classified according to :",
      "answer":"Power, Urgency, and Legitimacy"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 29",
      "question":"In what stage of Risk Management do you determine the Impact of Risks on the project ?",
      "answer":"Perform Qualitative Analysis"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 30",
      "question":"The costs of nonconformance include all of the following listed below with the exception of :",
      "answer":"Quality Training"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 31",
      "question":"A project manager is highly Skeptical of his team members. He constantly monitors their everytmove and doubts their performance. The project manager can be considered to be a:",
      "answer":"Theory X Manager"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 32",
      "question":"What is your analysis of a situation whereby the Earned Value of your project is lesser thantPlanned Value and if the performance of the project were to continue the same way:",
      "answer":"The project will be behind schedule when it completes"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 33",
      "question":"Which report would you utilize as a project manager to show the actual performance versus thetplanned performance on a project ?",
      "answer":"Variance Report"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 34",
      "question":"The Project Charter is vital to every project because while work is being done, the charter istmost useful for",
      "answer":"Determining whether the work being done is in line with the projecttcharter"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 35",
      "question":"Which of the following best describes the benefit of Colocation for a Project :",
      "answer":"Helps build communication between the team"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 36",
      "question":"Which of the following issues the project charter ?",
      "answer":"Sponsor"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 37",
      "question":"The project team identifies a risk and shares information on it with the Project Manager. Aftertextensive discussions with the management, a strategy is developed to deal with it. It istdecided that it is in the best interest of the project to allow the risk to happen. Which typetof Risk Response Strategy is being used?",
      "answer":"Exploit"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 38",
      "question":"While project work is being executed, a team member informs you that she is uncertain of exactlytwhat sort of work she needs to do. Which of the following documents would you share with her totensure she reads detailed information regarding work packages ?",
      "answer":"WBS Dictionary"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 39",
      "question":"A stakeholder in your company has a regular habit of requesting multiple changes on projects.tWhat is the ideal approach a project manager can take to handle this situation at the beginningtof the project?",
      "answer":"Involve the stakeholder on the project as early as possible"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 40",
      "question":"On projects, certain risks are kept on the watch list. These risks are considered by the projecttmanager as :",
      "answer":"Low Priority"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 41",
      "question":"Which of the following represents the To complete Performance Index ?",
      "answer":"(BAC-EV)/ (BAC-AC)"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 42",
      "question":"Consider yourself as the Seller. From amongst the contracts listed below, for which of them wouldtyou pay the most attention to when it comes to the scope of the project?",
      "answer":"Fixed Price"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 43",
      "question":"_____________ focuses on the most difficult issues and presents information in terms of order oftpriority.",
      "answer":"Pareto Diagram"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 44",
      "question":"A project manager is expected to possess various important abilities. Which leadership aspect istconsidered to be the most important for a project manager to have?",
      "answer":"To be a strong communicator"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 45",
      "question":"Secondary risks refer to:",
      "answer":"Risks which are created by risk responses"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 46",
      "question":"The optimistic estimate for an activity is 15 days, and the pessimistic estimate is 27. What istthe standard deviation for the activity ?",
      "answer":"2"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 47",
      "question":"____________ motivation theory is concerned with how the salary and working conditions of atworkplace do not lead to improved levels of motivation for the employees.",
      "answer":"Herzberg"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 48",
      "question":"While working on your project, the senior management contacts you directly and requests sometchanges to be made on the project. What is the First thing you should do as a project manager?",
      "answer":"Understand the scope of the change being requested"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 49",
      "question":"A Project Manager is working on a big budget international  website development project forta company that is based in over 32 countries. She happens to come across some of her colleaguestfrom the other offices who are meant to be the primary users of the new website. They mentiontthat they have some concerns about the user interface design as the website is not that easy totnavigate. The Project manager listens to their feedback and then reports it to the sponsor whiletsuggesting changes to the scope. Which of the following is the best description of the projecttmanagers action:",
      "answer":"Stakeholder Analysis"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 50",
      "question":"While managing a project that has several stakeholder requests for changes, which of thetfollowing is the best description of when would you decide to change the scope baseline?",
      "answer":"When you have received the approval for the changes."
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 51",
      "question":"During project executing, a project manager uses team meetings in order to (Choose thetBest answer):",
      "answer":"Communicate"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 52",
      "question":"The following Chart allows a project manager to consider how many resources were used on atmonthly basis on a project:",
      "answer":"Resource Histogram"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 53",
      "question":"Your senior management wants to evaluate the performance of your project with reference to thetprevious projects in your industry domain. What should you provide your management with?",
      "answer":"Benchmarks"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 54",
      "question":"Which of the following involves the collection, integration and distribution of informationtregarding outputs of the project management processes?",
      "answer":"Project Management Information System"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 55",
      "question":"As a project manager, for which of the following situations would you consider that a customerthas accepted the entire project as complete?",
      "answer":"You have received formal sign off and formal acceptance from the customer"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 56",
      "question":"A global scale software application project includes multiple risks. These include :tA 30 percent probability of a 15 day delay in the coding process    tA 40 percent probability of a 10 day delay in the user interface design process    tA 10 percent probability of a 20 day delay in the online integration    tWhat would be the EMV ( Expected Monetary Value) of the project?",
      "answer":"10.5 days"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 57",
      "question":"The budget for a project designated $2000 for work performed and till this point in time, hastspent $5000. If the budget had included $7000 for the work scheduled on the project, what is thetvalue of the cost variance (CV)",
      "answer":"(3000)"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 58",
      "question":"While working with suppliers,  Communications related to contracts should be",
      "answer":"Formal Written Communication"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 59",
      "question":"You are the project manager working on a large scale office building construction project for onetof the leading technology companies in the world. Given the amount of scope left to betcompleted, you will require more time to finish the project. What is the Best decision to maketat this moment?",
      "answer":"Come up with ways to compress the schedule and share them with management"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 60",
      "question":"Buffers are used in the project schedule to act as a cushion for",
      "answer":"Risks"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 61",
      "question":"Which of the following theory includes the concepts of Self Actualization,Security and Esteem:",
      "answer":"Maslow"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 62",
      "question":"While working on a real estate housing construction project in a mountainous area, you realizetthat the previously identified risk of thunderstorms is inevitable. If there is no appropriatetresponse to this risk, what response strategy would you use?",
      "answer":"Acceptance"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 63",
      "question":"Your project team member mentions that people from different departments keep asking him to dotperform various tasks for them. You are working in a functional organization, which of thetfollowing has the authority to give directions to this team member?",
      "answer":"The Functional Manager"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 64",
      "question":"On projects , documents which are collected as historical records are archived for futuretprojects during which of the following?",
      "answer":"Project Closure"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 65",
      "question":"Which of the following refers to performance requirements :",
      "answer":"What the product should be able to do"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 66",
      "question":"Based on the current work schedule on the project, you decide that 3:30pm on Fridays is thetcorrect time for team to submit their project status reports. What is the best type oftcommunication to convey this to the team:",
      "answer":"Informal Written Communication"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 67",
      "question":"The estimated value of work completed is represented most appropriately by the term:",
      "answer":"Earned Value"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 68",
      "question":"At one of the project team meetings, it is decided certain extra functionalities will be added totthe customers website to provide more value. Why is this not encouraged as a practice ?",
      "answer":"This is considered as Gold Plating"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 69",
      "question":"How would a project manager interpret the performance of a project if it's SPI (Schedule tPerformance Index) has a value of 0.95?",
      "answer":"You are progressing at 95 percent of the rate that was originally planned"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 70",
      "question":"On a project, an activity has an Early Start of day 5, A late start of day 16, an early finish oft day 12, and a late finish of day 23. What is the float of the activity ?",
      "answer":"11"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 71",
      "question":"You have been assigned a construction project in a new city you just moved in to. There are overt300 potential stakeholders on the project, What is the best way to movetforward?",
      "answer":"Figure out a way in which you can effectively collect the needs of all thetstakeholders"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 72",
      "question":"One of your stakeholders has suggested a  change in the form of a new process that cant improve efficiency on the project. However, it will also cause a change in scope to the projecttwork. What should you as a project manager do FIRST?",
      "answer":"Analyze the risks of implementing the change"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 73",
      "question":"The following statement is correct in describing a risk rating matrix used on a project:",
      "answer":"The risk rating matrix is standardized between projects"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 74",
      "question":"The control chart for your project states that the last 15 computer chipboards manufactured weretoutside of the lower control limit. What should you do immediately as a project manager?",
      "answer":"Halt the production"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 75",
      "question":"Which conflict resolution technique would allow you to come up with a solution that would have at long lasting effect?",
      "answer":"Problem Solving"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 76",
      "question":"What is the most effective way to get a group of over 1000 stakeholders to share their trequirements regarding the project?",
      "answer":"Questionnaires"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 77",
      "question":"You need to get intensive research done on a technological component to be included as part oftyour final project deliverable. You are in the process of determining whether you should get thetresearch done in house or whether you should outsource it to a Specialized research firm. Whichtprocess are you in currently?",
      "answer":"Plan Procurement"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 78",
      "question":"There are various types of meetings on a project. What is the purpose of having Status meetingston a project?",
      "answer":"To exchange information regarding the project"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 79",
      "question":"Your customer is very particular about ensuring that you keep the costs low on the housingtprojects you have been assigned as a project manager on. What costs do you need to take intotaccount which will help you keep the customers goal in mind?",
      "answer":"Variable and Direct"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 80",
      "question":"You are working on a project that involves the development of an enterprise level software. Thetcustomer has conveyed his dissatisfaction with how the project is performing. Upon checking, youtnotice that the project is performing perfectly well as per the baselines which were originallytdecided upon. What is the FIRST thing you should do as project manager?",
      "answer":"Have a meeting with the customer"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 81",
      "question":"While working on your project, you encountered a complicated problem that involved multipletstakeholders and processes. You took a decision to tackle the situation and executed yourtsolution. A year later, you notice the same problem has reoccurred. What did youtmost likely not do ?",
      "answer":"Confirmed that your decision solved the problem at hand"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 82",
      "question":"As a project manager, In what situation would Formal Written communication be most relevant whentinteracting with the customer on a project ?",
      "answer":"When the customer wants to add more features to the final product"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 83",
      "question":"In your years of experience, you have accumulated vast and specialized knowledge on the projecttmanagement discipline. What is the best way to use that knowledge ?",
      "answer":"You should share your knowledge with the world by transmitting it throughtlectures, presentations, articles, books etc."
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 84",
      "question":"The Actual cost is $42000, the planned value is $32000 and the earned value is $34000. What istthe schedule variance ?",
      "answer":"$2000"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 85",
      "question":"Which of the following  is the BEST for completing lessons learned ?",
      "answer":"The Stakeholders"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 86",
      "question":"You are assigned as a project manager in another country to develop a crucial project with globaltimplications for your organization. You are requested to make a payment to the country officialstso that they may authorize the work order. What should be your decision ?",
      "answer":"Consult with your legal team to see if the payment falls under a bribe"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 87",
      "question":"A project manager may find the following tool to be the most useful in coming up with the besttprice from the sellers :",
      "answer":"Independent Estimate"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 88",
      "question":"As a project manager for a yearlong project, you have had regular meetings with stakeholderstsince the past 11 months. The team is working efficiently, and so far the project has beentconsistently on budget and on schedule. However, the stakeholders have expressed theirtdissatisfaction with the project deliverables which will end up delaying the project by twotmonths. Which of the following could have prevented such circumstances ?",
      "answer":"Define Scope"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 89",
      "question":"As a newly assigned project manager on a large scale international project, Kate has recentlytdeveloped the risk responses to handle the high ranking risks from the prioritized list oftrisks. Kate is preparing to proceed to the control risks process when Dave ( A colleague andtfellow project manager from another project) reminds her of an important task she left out intthe Plan Risk Response Process. What did Dave tell her ?",
      "answer":"Kate, you forgot to analyze the secondary risks"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 90",
      "question":"\"Quality is Planned in, It is not inspected in\". What is the best represented significance oftthis phrase to you as a project manager ?",
      "answer":"It leads to lesser costs/expensive  and improves the quality"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 91",
      "question":"The project status reports for the month are due in two days time. One of the team memberstmentions to you that some of the other members of the team have not been accurately reportingtthe number of hours being spent on the project's activities. As the project manager, what actiontshould you take first?",
      "answer":"Provide accurate information in the project status reports"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 92",
      "question":"Who creates the WBS ?",
      "answer":"Project Team"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 93",
      "question":"The configuration management includes multiple processes. Which of the following does not belongtto configuration management ?",
      "answer":"Configuration Closure"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 94",
      "question":"A project manager would consider all of the following as buffers EXCEPT :",
      "answer":"Extra Buffer"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 95",
      "question":"Organization put a strong emphasis on the creation of lessons learned documents. What is the mosttrelevant use of lessons learned ?",
      "answer":"To serve as historical records for projects in the future."
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 96",
      "question":"After the Plan Risk Responses process, you notice there are residual risks left on the project.tWhat should you do ?",
      "answer":"You should document the risks and revisit them later to see if any actiontneeds to be taken"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 97",
      "question":"The company you are working at is currently going through downsizing due to slow economictconditions globally.  Every team is going through layoffs and it is inevitable that some oftyour team members will be next in line. Your team is discussing this topic constantly, so youtdecide to add your thoughts by saying \"Dont worry about it , we will simply improve ourtperformance and that will help protect us from getting layed off\".  Which of the followingttechniques do you think your actions represent:",
      "answer":"Smoothing"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 98",
      "question":"If the Actual Cost = 450 , Earned Value = 400 and Planned Value = 350 , What is the value of thetCost Variance ?",
      "answer":"-50"
   },
   {
      "title":"问题 99",
      "question":"A project you are working on has a payback period of 11 months. What does this signify?",
      "answer":"The project will take 11 months to cover its costs and then start to generatetrevenue"
   }
]